[{"answer": "I said", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " I'd like to spoil him just once. Sure you don't want me to go in with you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Why, I'm surprised, Mr. my friend. That's no way to talk to your wife", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Hello, my friend.  Hi, my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " I notice you still remember it", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You know, my friend, I sort of wish you hadn't done it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "That's the first time you've been right today. That's what I", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You bet I've got a better offer", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I know, my friend, but I", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You wouldn't have taken me if I hadn't been dol", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Where'd you meet this man", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "that place... my friend, eh", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What's his line", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " The insurance business", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh sure, it's honest. But somehow, I can't picture you with a guy who sells policies", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He does, does he? How did I treat you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, I can, and I love it! He forgets the office when he's with me. He doesn't treat me like an erran", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't know about water buffaloes, but I know about him. He's kind and sweet and considerate. He wants a home", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Attaboy!  Come on, my friend", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Where are we going? I'm going to buy you two lunch", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Well, so you're getting married tomorrow, eh? How does it feel, my friend", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Taking the train today", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "He comes by it naturally. His grandfather was a snake", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "That's what he did to me. Swept me right off my feet", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "If he's nuts, why doesn't the State just put him away", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " The colored vote happens to be very important to the Mayor of this town", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "How can you have any happiness after that? All through the years you'll remember that a man went to the gallows because you were too selfish to wait two hours! I tell you, my friend' face will come between you on the train tonight", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What do you mean, only an act? Haven't you got any feeling", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " What do you think I am", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "All right. The check will be certified. Want my fingerprints", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I know a lot of men who didn't do anything till they met my friend. Please, dear", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I'll be careful, darling. You be, please", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Oh, sure.  Well, thanks for everything", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "So long", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Miss my friend. She's a wonderful person", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Yes. Isn't she beautiful", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Phone for you, my friend", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Oh, some insurance man. Are you in", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " We'll have to satisfy them. What would you say to giving them a joint interview? I could give them some of the psychological aspects of the case and you could give them the legal aspects", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Yes, shaking hands. I don't take a very good picture, though", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "All right. You can't. But tomorrow the Post will run the story of that roulette game on 43rd Street that your brothe", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You can let him out on bail, can't you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " Yes, wasn't it", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " I'm sure you haven't any", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "If the Mayor wants me, he knows where I am", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What went off", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What went off", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "A fine fai", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Four of Mr. my friend's Deputy Sheriffs were rushed to the hospital", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " The names are my friend, who is the Mayor's brothe", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Well, there's a lot of Communistic sympathizers around", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "But we're going to hang him, my friend. He can't get away", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "They were all standing around when he wrote it. It was after they got back from fishing", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": " You can't get him on the phone. He's out duckshooting now", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "What is it", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Tell 'em to hold the wire", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "They got him!  Wait a minute", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I did.  Hold the wire", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": " Will you try", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " Here", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " So long, nothing! Where's my friend's wallet", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " You know it is", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "No", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Maybe you're my friend and maybe you're not", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "No, no, you're right. I don't want to kill anybody. All I want to do is be let alone", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "What are you doing", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I won't shut up! That girl killed herself. O", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Where do you think you're going", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": " Get Bruce out of jail! How can you worry about a man who's resting comfortably in a quiet police station while this is going on? my friend, this is war! You can't desert now", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": " Get Bruce out of jail! How can you worry about a man who's resting comfortably in a quiet police station while this is going on? my friend, this is war! You can't desert now", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "You drooling idiot! What do you mean, you're getting out! There are three hundred and sixt", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Whoa", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "That one", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "No, I was going to give it to her", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Did you give her the money", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Then suppose you give me the money. Four hundred and fifty dollars", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "my friend? Oh", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Railroad tickets", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Railroad tickets", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "Didn't you hear him? Of course he's coming back here. Keep going, will you", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "Tear into it, will you? Don't sit there like a frozen robin", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "Finished", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Who is it", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": " It's my friend", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "Which ought to be about three hours more, I'd say", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "And your arrest. You'll each get about ten years, I think", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "How was that for a tight squeeze", "docId": "His-Girl-Friday.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "Worried! I was petrified. Weren't you", "qsentId": 90}]